https://www.childsafehouse.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
CHILD ABUSE/NEGLECT HOTLINE: 1.800.392.3738
FacebookTwitterLinkedinInstagram
Be a Hero
Child Safe of Central Missouri, Inc. takes the privacy of our website, website users and the security of their personal information very seriously. We will not sell, trade, or share your personal data with anyone. The purpose of this privacy policy is to establish the principles that govern our use of personal data that we may obtain about you. By using this website or by registering as a user of the services that we provide, you agree to this use.
Child Safe of Central Missouri, Inc. will collect personal data, such as identifying information, contact information or professional information, when it is voluntarily submitted to us. We monitor the use of our website by collecting usage data through marketing automation and analytics tools as well. These tools may collect information about you such as computer or device information, location information, demographic information, behavioral information and more. We may refer to collected personal data to better understand how we can serve you. We will not transfer this information to any third party unless disclosed to you.
A cookie is a small piece of information sent to a web browser, which enables a server to recognize visitors. Cookies are widely used in order to make websites work or work more efficiently, as well as to provide website owners with information about the use of their website. Child Safe of Central Missouri, Inc. uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. Some functions of the website may not be available if cookies are disabled.
Content on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
This website is not intended to attract children under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect personal data from or about any person under the age of 16.
We utilize technology and policies to protect your privacy from unauthorized access and improper use. We update these as new technologies become available.
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page. Please check back to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy. The date at the bottom of this page indicates when this privacy policy was last updated.
If you have questions about our privacy policy, please email
info@childsafehouse.org. Thank you.
Last Updated: 9/23/19
Stay up-to-date! Sign up to receive the latest info.
Email:
Child Safe of Central Missouri Serves 11 Counties BentonCarrollCharitonHenryJohnsonLafayetteLinnMoniteauMorganPettisSaline
